{"sid": "6XPYTVFK3SJC_main", "calc_equals_delay": 5, "block_data": {"block_0": {"mean_level": 10, "start_time": 456605, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "300", "question_time_start": 456608, "question": "9+17+44", "correct_answer": 70, "events": [["submit", 460151]], "time_left_end": "297", "answered_time": 460151, "user_answer": "70", "user_correct": "True", "score": "1"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "297", "question_time_start": 460151, "question": "47+417", "correct_answer": 464, "events": [["submit", 463955]], "time_left_end": "293", "answered_time": 463955, "user_answer": "464", "user_correct": "True", "score": "2"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "293", "question_time_start": 463956, "question": "68+83+56+83", "correct_answer": 290, "events": [["calc_6", 466174], ["calc_8", 466439], ["calc_+", 467102], ["calc_8", 467802], ["calc_3", 468141], ["calc_+", 468488], ["calc_5", 469055], ["calc_6", 469238], ["calc_+", 469687], ["calc_8", 470212], ["calc_3", 470546], ["calc_=", 470944], ["submit", 478059]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "279", "answered_time": 478059, "user_answer": "290", "user_correct": "True", "score": "3"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "279", "question_time_start": 478059, "question": "44+24+17+34", "correct_answer": 119, "events": [["submit", 481595]], "time_left_end": "276", "answered_time": 481595, "user_answer": "119", "user_correct": "True", "score": "4"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "276", "question_time_start": 481598, "question": "76+176", "correct_answer": 252, "events": [["submit", 484428]], "time_left_end": "273", "answered_time": 484428, "user_answer": "252", "user_correct": "True", "score": "5"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "273", "question_time_start": 484428, "question": "74+66+48+817", "correct_answer": 1005, "events": [["submit", 496421]], "time_left_end": "261", "answered_time": 496421, "user_answer": "1005", "user_correct": "True", "score": "6"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "261", "question_time_start": 496421, "question": "47+69+759", "correct_answer": 875, "events": [["submit", 507027]], "time_left_end": "250", "answered_time": 507027, "user_answer": "916", "user_correct": "False", "score": "5"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "250", "question_time_start": 507027, "question": "78+37+277", "correct_answer": 392, "events": [["submit", 521307]], "time_left_end": "236", "answered_time": 521307, "user_answer": "392", "user_correct": "True", "score": "6"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "236", "question_time_start": 521307, "question": "83+44+28+16", "correct_answer": 171, "events": [["submit", 526567]], "time_left_end": "231", "answered_time": 526567, "user_answer": "221", "user_correct": "False", "score": "5"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "231", "question_time_start": 526568, "question": "6+49+44", "correct_answer": 99, "events": [["submit", 530137]], "time_left_end": "227", "answered_time": 530137, "user_answer": "99", "user_correct": "True", "score": "6"}}}, "block_1": {"mean_level": 10, "start_time": 530137, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "227", "question_time_start": 530137, "question": "64+19+14+73", "correct_answer": 170, "events": [["submit", 533788]], "time_left_end": "223", "answered_time": 533788, "user_answer": "", "user_correct": "False", "score": "5"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "223", "question_time_start": 533789, "question": "23+929", "correct_answer": 952, "events": [["submit", 537538]], "time_left_end": "220", "answered_time": 537538, "user_answer": "952", "user_correct": "True", "score": "6"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "220", "question_time_start": 537539, "question": "6+47+77", "correct_answer": 130, "events": [["submit", 540642]], "time_left_end": "216", "answered_time": 540642, "user_answer": "130", "user_correct": "True", "score": "7"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "216", "question_time_start": 540642, "question": "86+856", "correct_answer": 942, "events": [["submit", 546957]], "time_left_end": "210", "answered_time": 546957, "user_answer": "942", "user_correct": "True", "score": "8"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "210", "question_time_start": 546957, "question": "38+93+26+78", "correct_answer": 235, "events": [["submit", 551818]], "time_left_end": "205", "answered_time": 551818, "user_answer": "235", "user_correct": "True", "score": "9"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "205", "question_time_start": 551819, "question": "49+57+344", "correct_answer": 450, "events": [["submit", 561282]], "time_left_end": "196", "answered_time": 561282, "user_answer": "450", "user_correct": "True", "score": "10"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "196", "question_time_start": 561283, "question": "43+43+619", "correct_answer": 705, "events": [["submit", 567610]], "time_left_end": "189", "answered_time": 567610, "user_answer": "706", "user_correct": "False", "score": "9"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "189", "question_time_start": 567610, "question": "24+46+69+94", "correct_answer": 233, "events": [["submit", 576428]], "time_left_end": "181", "answered_time": 576428, "user_answer": "233", "user_correct": "True", "score": "10"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "181", "question_time_start": 576429, "question": "16+77+58+438", "correct_answer": 589, "events": [["submit", 585908]], "time_left_end": "171", "answered_time": 585907, "user_answer": "589", "user_correct": "True", "score": "11"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "171", "question_time_start": 585913, "question": "9+29+58", "correct_answer": 96, "events": [["submit", 588879]], "time_left_end": "168", "answered_time": 588879, "user_answer": "96", "user_correct": "True", "score": "12"}}}, "block_2": {"mean_level": 10, "start_time": 588881, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "168", "question_time_start": 588881, "question": "87+13+48+73", "correct_answer": 221, "events": [["submit", 597886]], "time_left_end": "159", "answered_time": 597886, "user_answer": "221", "user_correct": "True", "score": "13"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "159", "question_time_start": 597886, "question": "48+63+26+59", "correct_answer": 196, "events": [["submit", 608718]], "time_left_end": "148", "answered_time": 608718, "user_answer": "196", "user_correct": "True", "score": "14"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "148", "question_time_start": 608718, "question": "53+49+63+269", "correct_answer": 434, "events": [["submit", 618036]], "time_left_end": "139", "answered_time": 618036, "user_answer": "434", "user_correct": "True", "score": "15"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "139", "question_time_start": 618036, "question": "89+386", "correct_answer": 475, "events": [["submit", 626964]], "time_left_end": "130", "answered_time": 626964, "user_answer": "465", "user_correct": "False", "score": "14"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "130", "question_time_start": 626965, "question": "98+83+333", "correct_answer": 514, "events": [["submit", 643570]], "time_left_end": "114", "answered_time": 643570, "user_answer": "514", "user_correct": "True", "score": "15"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "114", "question_time_start": 643570, "question": "76+918", "correct_answer": 994, "events": [["submit", 646692]], "time_left_end": "110", "answered_time": 646692, "user_answer": "994", "user_correct": "True", "score": "16"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "110", "question_time_start": 646692, "question": "6+48+86", "correct_answer": 140, "events": [["submit", 649988]], "time_left_end": "107", "answered_time": 649988, "user_answer": "140", "user_correct": "True", "score": "17"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "107", "question_time_start": 649988, "question": "28+74+77+17", "correct_answer": 196, "events": [["submit", 655912]], "time_left_end": "101", "answered_time": 655912, "user_answer": "196", "user_correct": "True", "score": "18"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "101", "question_time_start": 655913, "question": "33+19+356", "correct_answer": 408, "events": [["submit", 662100]], "time_left_end": "95", "answered_time": 662100, "user_answer": "408", "user_correct": "True", "score": "19"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "95", "question_time_start": 662101, "question": "4+56+57", "correct_answer": 117, "events": [["submit", 664582]], "time_left_end": "93", "answered_time": 664582, "user_answer": "117", "user_correct": "True", "score": "20"}}}, "block_3": {"mean_level": 10, "start_time": 664583, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "93", "question_time_start": 664583, "question": "26+44+87+98", "correct_answer": 255, "events": [["submit", 670589]], "time_left_end": "87", "answered_time": 670589, "user_answer": "275", "user_correct": "False", "score": "19"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "87", "question_time_start": 670590, "question": "4+79+54", "correct_answer": 137, "events": [["submit", 674585]], "time_left_end": "83", "answered_time": 674585, "user_answer": "137", "user_correct": "True", "score": "20"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "83", "question_time_start": 674585, "question": "18+93+14+293", "correct_answer": 418, "events": [["submit", 688724]], "time_left_end": "68", "answered_time": 688724, "user_answer": "418", "user_correct": "True", "score": "21"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "68", "question_time_start": 688724, "question": "78+148", "correct_answer": 226, "events": [["submit", 693345]], "time_left_end": "64", "answered_time": 693345, "user_answer": "226", "user_correct": "True", "score": "22"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "64", "question_time_start": 693347, "question": "84+58+87+59", "correct_answer": 288, "events": [["submit", 698990]], "time_left_end": "58", "answered_time": 698990, "user_answer": "288", "user_correct": "True", "score": "23"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "58", "question_time_start": 698991, "question": "67+33+923", "correct_answer": 1023, "events": [["submit", 702378]], "time_left_end": "55", "answered_time": 702378, "user_answer": "1023", "user_correct": "True", "score": "24"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "55", "question_time_start": 702380, "question": "16+239", "correct_answer": 255, "events": [["submit", 709156]], "time_left_end": "48", "answered_time": 709156, "user_answer": "255", "user_correct": "True", "score": "25"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "48", "question_time_start": 709157, "question": "14+68+777", "correct_answer": 859, "events": [["submit", 721587]], "time_left_end": "36", "answered_time": 721587, "user_answer": "859", "user_correct": "True", "score": "26"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "36", "question_time_start": 721588, "question": "97+29+39+26", "correct_answer": 191, "events": [["submit", 729850]], "time_left_end": "27", "answered_time": 729850, "user_answer": "191", "user_correct": "True", "score": "27"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "27", "question_time_start": 729851, "question": "6+83+83", "correct_answer": 172, "events": [["submit", 734153]], "time_left_end": "23", "answered_time": 734153, "user_answer": "172", "user_correct": "True", "score": "28"}}}, "block_4": {"mean_level": 10, "start_time": 734153, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "23", "question_time_start": 734153, "question": "43+69+53+49", "correct_answer": 214, "events": [["submit", 749932]], "time_left_end": "7", "answered_time": 749932, "user_answer": "214", "user_correct": "True", "score": "29"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "7", "question_time_start": 749932, "question": "13+29+67+19", "correct_answer": 128, "events": [["submit", 754901]], "time_left_end": "2", "answered_time": 754901, "user_answer": "128", "user_correct": "True", "score": "30"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "2", "question_time_start": 754902, "question": "93+933", "correct_answer": 1026, "events": []}}}}}